ILR School CAHRS Audio-Visual Materials /4304 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School CAHRS Audio-Visual Materials
1999-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Center for Advanced Human Resource Studies
/4304 AV
2.44 cubic feet
2.4 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
The ILR School CAHRS Audio-Visual Materials collection consists of video recordings of guest lectures.
8238020
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 23, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4304: ILR School CAHRS Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Center for Advanced Human Resource Studies
8238020
- CAHRS executive guest lectures (on tape) (Box 1)
  - Unlabeled, 1 (Box 1)
  - Bob Corcoran GE - October 8, 2002, 2 (Box 1)
  - CHARS-ILR School, Cornell University - Guest Lecture, 10/11/00: Stephen H. Leven, Texas Instruments, 2000; 3 (Box 1)
  - Center for Advanced Human Resource Studies - Cornell University: Executive Guest Lecture: John Murabito 10/24/01, 2001; 4 (Box 1)
  - Press Conference to introduce David J. Skorton as the 12th President of Cornell University, 5 (Box 1)
  - CAHRS - Cornell University: Federico Castellanos, IBM -- Developing Global Leaders and Culture at IBM, 6 (Box 1)
  - College of Industrial & Labor Relations: Cornell University Center for Advanced Human Resources Studies: Marcia Avedon Developing Leadership at Honeywell -- 3/5/02, 2002; 7 (Box 1)
  - Center for Advanced Human Resources - CAHRS Cornell University: Robert Gonzales, Fidelity 11/20/03, 8 (Box 1)
  - Cornell University ILR, CAHRS Executive Lecture Series: Andy Rich, Charles Schwab Co. 11/15/00, 2000; 9 (Box 1)
  - Tomorrow's Work, Today's Decisions (Workplace 2000 Conference, 3/92), 1992; 10 (Box 1)
  - Business day Air date: 02/26/97, 1997; 11 (Box 1)
  - CAHR Guest Lecturer, 12 (Box 1)
  - Cornell University ILR, CAHRS Executive Lecture Series: Andy Rich, Charles Schwab Co. 11/15/00, 2000; 13 (Box 1)
  - CAHRS - ILR School, Cornell University - Guest Lecture, 10/11/00: Stephen H. Leven, Texas Instruments, 2000; 14 (Box 1)
  - OHD: Making the Business Case for Human Resource Investments: Pt. 1, tape 2 of 2 -- 6/7/99, 1999; 15 (Box 1)
  - OHD: Making the Business Case for Human Resource Investments: Pt. 2, tape 1 of 2 -- 6/7/99, 1999; 16 (Box 1)
  - OHD: Making the Business Case for Human Resource Investments: Pt. 2, tape 2 -- 6/7/99, 1999; 17 (Box 1)
  - HR: Blown to Bits: 6/28/00, 2000; 18 (Box 1)
  - HR: Blown to Bits: 6/28/00, 2000; 19 (Box 1)
  - Pam Step - 3/12/02, 2002; 20 (Box 1)
  - JAM, 21 (Box 1)
- OHD: Making the Business Case for Human Resource Investments - Pt. 1, tape 1 of 2: 6/7/99, 1999; 1 (Box 2)
- GTE HR Balanced Scorecard Shaping the Business Proposition through Measurement, 2 (Box 2)
- CAHRS Raytheon Domic Donovon - Final Cut, 3 (Box 2)
- SUTA HRPS Edited, 4 (Box 2)
- SOTA, 5 (Box 2)
- SOTA presentation gg Wright-Dyer-Takia, 6 (Box 2)
- HRPS 1999: 3/31/99, 7 (Box 2)
- ILR MacDonald/Bahr/Bronfenbrenner Int. & Class, 8 (Box 2)
- CAHRS Lecture: 6 Mar 00, 2000; 9 (Box 2)
- Raytheon Edited, 10 (Box 2)
- CAHRS - Randy MacDonald Lecture Excerpts: 3/6/00, 2000; 11 (Box 2)
- HRPS 1999 - tape 6: 3/31/99, 1 (Box 3)
- HRPS 1999 Tape 7: 3/31/99, 2 (Box 3)
- CAHRS - Randy McDonald - 2 - 3/6/00, 2000; 3 (Box 3)
- CAHRS - Randy McDonald - 3: 3/6/00, 2000; 4 (Box 3)
- CAHRS: Randy McDonald - 1 -- 3/6/00, 2000; 5 (Box 3)
- Raytheon, 6 (Box 3)
- CAHRS - Randy McDonald - 3/6/00, 2000; 7 (Box 3)
- ILR David Nachbor Lecture - 4/3/01, 2001; 8 (Box 3)
  Scope and Contents
  camera original
- The Indus Tour: A Self-Guided Orientation (Box 4)
  - The Indus Tour: A Self-Guided Orientation, 1 (Box 4)
- The Indus Tour: A Self-Guided Orientation (Box 5)
  - The Indus Tour: A Self-Guided Orientation, 1 (Box 5)
- CAHRS - Randy MacDonald (Box 6)
  - CAHRS - Randy MacDonald, 1 (Box 6)
- Dennis Donovan '99; HR SOTA '99; Video Stream files (Box 7)
  - Dennis Donovan '99; HR SOTA '99; Video Stream files, 1999; 1 (Box 7)